login.wiki 2015-06-02

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your personally identifiable information in accordance with our website.

#### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog or website?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

#### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, search the website, or use of certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To quickly process your transaction.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

#### How do we protect visitor information?

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited numbers of persons who have  special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via secure sockets layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user  enters, submits, accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

#### Do we use ‘cookies’?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your trousers help menu to  learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn off cookies, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However you can still place orders.

#### How does our site handle do not track signals?

We honour do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

#### Does our site allow third-party behavioural tracking?

It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioural tracking.

#### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the children’s online privacy protection act COPPA puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission enforces the COPPA rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

#### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties you are personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who will assist us in operating our website, conducting business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, and force our site policies, or protect ours for others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

#### Third-party links

Occasionally, as our discretion, we may include offer a third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Google

Google advertising requirements can be summed up by Google advertising principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense advertising our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users are based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may hot out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

  * We have implemented the following:
  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google display network impression reporting
  * Demographics and interests reporting
  * Double-click platform integration

We along with third party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the double-click cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile darter regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other service  functions as they relate to our website.

_Opting out:_

_Users can set  preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings Page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add-on._

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA  is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operate a website collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to  post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.OFdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

Users come visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our homepage, or at a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website. Our privacy policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’,  and can be easily found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

  * On our privacy policy page.

Users are able to change their personal information:

  * By emailing us

#### Fair Information Practices

The fair information practices principles from the backbone of privacy law in the US and the concept they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the fair information practice principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with fair information practices we will take the following response and action, should a data breach occurr: Within seven business days we will notify the users via in site notification.

We also agreed to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

#### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN SPAM Act  is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, its recipients the rights to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells and tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

  *  Send information, response to enquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  *  Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with the CAN SPAM Act we agree to the following:

  * Not to use false or misleading subjects or email addresses
  * To identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
  * To include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
  * To monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used
  * To honour opt out/unsubscribe requests quickly
  * To allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of the email

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can:

  *  Follow the instructions of the bottom of the email.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

Orlando Media  
Cann Rawar  
Oughterard  
Galway  
Ireland

## Share this article
